A Guide to the Lewis and Minor Families Papers
University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library, #3988
Lewis and Minor Families Papers 1730-1965
University of Virginia. Library. Special Collections Dept. Alderman Library University of Virginia Charlottesville, Virginia 22903 USA
3988
ca. 150 items
W.H. Landon White and Ida E. White
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
This collection was bequeathed to the University of Virginia Library by W.H. Landon White and Ida E. White on December 6, 1979.
Container List
- Correspondence
  - Correspondence of the Minor Family, 1829-1897 (Box Box 1)
  - Letters to Launcelot Minor Blackford, 1855-1862 (Box Box 1)
  - Letters to Lewis Willis Minor, 1848-1871 (Box Box 1)
  - Letters to William Henry Landon White, 1903-1945 (Box Box 1)
  - Lewis Willis Minor to James Monroe Minor, 1828-1855 (Box Box 1)
  - Lewis Willis Minor to Lucy Landon Minor, 1846-1853 (Box Box 1)
  - Lewis Willis Minor to Mary B. (Minor) Blackford, 1846-1866 (Box Box 1)
  - Lewis Willis Minor to William M. Blackford, 1847-1860 (Box Box 1)
- Topical
  - Certificates of William Henry Landon White, 1889-1918 (Box Box 2)
  - Civil War: Confederate Bonds and Money, 1862-1864 (Box Box 2)
  - Civil War: Hospital Book--Register of Patients, etc., 1861-1863 (Box Box 2)
  - Civil War: Terms of Surrender of Confederate Naval Forces in Alabama, 1865 May 4 (Box Box 2)
  - Genealogy of the Carter Family and Minor Family (Box Box 2)
  - Legal Papers of Eloise Innerarity Minor, 1872-1890 (Box Box 2)
  - Legal Papers of Lewis Willis Minor, 1856-1871, n.d. (Box Box 2)
  - Legal Papers re dispute between Lewis Willis Minor and Archibald H. Gillespie, 1840-1854 (Box Box 2)
  - Legal Papers re Florida Property, 1879-1888 (Box Box 2)
  - Legal Papers: Will of Robert "King" Carter(copies), [1730] (Box Box 2)
  - Legal Papers: Miscellaneous, 1867-1920, n.d. (Box Box 2)
  - Medical Papers of Lewis Willis Minor, 1830-1876 (Box Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous, 1881-1954, n.d. (Box Box 2)
  - Notes of Lectures on Corporation Finance, 1932 (Box Box 2)